legalshield.com 2019-10-28

# Privacy Policy | LegalShield

Keeping customer information private is a priority for LegalShield, its subsidiaries and affiliates. To enable us to provide our membership plans, we need to collect certain personal information from you. It is sometimes necessary to share that personal information with others to provide our services to you. However, we want to emphasize that we are committed to maintaining the privacy of this information in accordance with law. All individuals with access to personal information about our customers are required to follow this policy.

This privacy notice informs you of what personal information we collect about you and how we treat that information. Its purpose is to answer questions you may have regarding our treatment of your personal information and reassures you of our dedication to keeping your personal information secure.

### Information We Collect

We collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms such as your name, address, payment instructions, Social Security Number and Social Insurance Number in Canada.
  * Information you may provide during visits to our website including IP address and cookies.
  * Information about your transactions, interactions or communications with us, our affiliates or others.

### Information We Share

We do not disclose any non-public personal information about our customers, past or present, to any non-affiliated entity except as described below and otherwise permitted by law. We may disclose all the information we collect, as described above, to Provider Law Firms and companies that assist us in the servicing or administration of the product you have requested or authorized.

When information is shared with companies that perform services on our behalf, we protect against the subsequent discloser of that information with a confidentiality agreement and/or other protective measures.

In no event do we disclose your personal information to companies that will use that information to contact you about their own products or services.

#### Our Security Procedures

We restrict access to non-public personal information to those persons who need such information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your non-public personal information. We keep information for as long as is necessary for our business purposes and will dispose of all information in appropriate ways according to law and our company practices.

#### Use of Cookies

LegalShield may use data collected from our website, including history data or cookies, in accordance with the Privacy Policy. Most of the cookies are functionality cookies which are used to recognize repeat visitors to the website. Analytics cookies are used to monitor how visitors use our website to give us understanding of what content visitors are viewing and where they spend time accessing it. Our website does not acknowledge Do Not Track settings. Third parties may also use cookies.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

LegalShield reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to revise, change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any material changes to the Privacy Policy will be incorporated on this page. Notice of changes may be given in any manner we choose in compliance with the law such as, but not limited to, posting a notice of changes on our websites. We encourage you to review this page periodically for the most recent version of the Privacy Policy. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is July 1, 2001. This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 28, 2019.

##### QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about this notice or if you would like to review or make changes to your personal information, please email us at memberservices@legalshield.com or  
Call us toll-free: (800) 654-7757 (US)  
(800) 440-8857 (Canada)  
(866) 274-5790 (TTY)
